Guide to the Mary Harron Papers MSS.608
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV. Film, 1939-2018; 13.48 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 1 small flat box, 1 large flat box, and 1 record carton; 19 audiocassettes; 17 VHS; 1 Video8; 1 U-matic; 21.86 Gigabytes in 556 computer files
  - Subseries IV.A. I Shot Andy Warhol, 1954-1997; 5.48 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes, 1 cassette box, 1 small flat box, and 1 large flat box; 2 audiocassettes; 3 VHS; 23.13 Megabytes in 24 computer files
    This subseries focuses on materials related to Harron's first feature film, I Shot Andy Warhol, which was released in 1996. The film is about Valerie Solanas, a 1960s radical feminist writer who was known for writing the SCUM Manifesto and shooting Andy Warhol. Materials consist of research material on Valerie Solanas, Andy Warhol, Maurice Girodias (Solanas's publisher) and feminist writing; transcripts and recordings of interviews; proposals and treatments; correspondence; production notes; contracts; casting notes; notebooks; shooting schedules; film elements (audio and video recordings on various media, both analog and digital); and press kits.
    - Audio Recordings
      - "I'm Set Free" -- Adele Bertei, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0179)
      - Score, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0067)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cast and Crew Lists, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Character Backgrounds, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Contracts, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - Electronic Records, 1993; FA_MSS_608_ER_6
      - Letters, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Legal Matters, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Lili Taylor's Annotated Script and Binder, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4-5, Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Media Recap, May 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Notebooks, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Original Prop -- SCUM Manifesto by Valerie Solanas, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Press
      - Clippings and Reviews, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10-11, Box 8, Folder 1-3, Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Press Kits, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Production Notes and Script Feedback, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Proposal and Treatments, 1992
      - BBC Treatment, FA_MSS_608_ER_5
      - Physical Copies (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Research Materials
      - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Culture and Politics of the 1960s, 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Fashion, Hair, and Makeup of the 1960s, 1967-1987 (Box 8, Folder 9, Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Feminist Writing, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Maurice Girodias and Olympia Press, 1967-1996 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
      - Interview Transcripts and Notes
        - Meredith Risen -- Interview Excerpts, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_7
        - Various Interviewees, circa 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Valerie Solanas
        - Biographical Material, Archival Correspondence, and Press, 1954-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
        - Graduation Photograph and Bail Slip, circa 1957-1968; FA_MSS_608_ER_8
        - Writing About, 1995-1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_9
        - Writing By, 1965-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - Andy Warhol and Factory Associates
        - Interviews, Articles, and Excerpts from Warhol's a, A Novel, 1966-1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        - Photographs, circa 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Screenings and Festivals, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1, Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Script by Mary Harron and Guinevere Turner
      - Early Versions, 1993; FA_MSS_608_ER_11
      - Later Version, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Set Binder, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Shooting Schedule, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Tape Logs, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ticket Sales, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Video Recordings
      - Compilation Tape, undated (Box 33, Vhs 608.0154)
      - I Shot Andy Warhol, April 6, 1995 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0005)
      - I Shot Andy Warhol, April 12, 1995 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0002)
  - Subseries IV.B. American Psycho, 1994-2000; 3.27 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes, 1 small flat box, and 1 cassette box; 1 VHS; 1 Video8; 2.37 Megabytes in 23 computer files
    This subseries consists of materials related to Harron's 2000 film, American Psycho, based on the novel by Bret Easton Ellis about an investment banker who is also a psychopathic killer. Materials include film elements (audio and video recordings on various media, both analog and digital); scripts; press and clippings; music cue sheets; storyboards; production photographs; and screening notes. Also included is the producers' response to controversy over the film's use of violence. Calls for boycotts began before the film started shooting.
    - Continuity, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence
      - Electronic Records, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_12
      - Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Editing Notes, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Music, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Notes
      - Electronic Records, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_13
      - Notebooks, circa 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Orchestral Score by John Cale, circa 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13, Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Post-Production Schedule, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Press
      - Clippings and Reviews, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1-8, Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Press Kits and Publicity Schedule, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Production Binder, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Production Photographs, circa 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Response to Pre-Production Media Storm over Violence in Film, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Scene Lists and Concepts
      - Electronic Records, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_14
      - Pull List, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Screening Comments, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay by Bret Easton Ellis, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay and Related Article by Norman Snider, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Script by Mary Harron and Guinevere Turner
      - Earliest Drafts, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
      - Electronic Drafts and Outtakes, 1996-1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_15
      - Green Draft and Revisions, March 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Storyboards, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Sundance Film Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Ticket Sales, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Video Recordings
      - Casting Session and Director's Session -- Dub, February 12, 1999 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0035)
      - "Crack Head #1" -- Junkie, Cathy, Miguel Interview, Yuppie Being Arrested, Legs on Broadway, Jim Tunan, undated (Box 29, Video8 608.0112)
    - Voiceover
      - Film Narration -- Excerpt, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Quotes from Book, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_16
  - Subseries IV.C. The Notorious Bettie Page, 1939-2006; 9.08 Linear Feet in 14 manuscript boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 1 small flat box, and 1 record carton; 17 audiocassettes; 11 VHS; 21.04 Gigabytes in 412 computer files
    This subseries consists of materials related to Harron's 2005 film, The Notorious Bettie Page. The film follows the life of Bettie Page, a pin-up model known for her bondage photographs, which became the target of Senate investigations into pornography and juvenile delinquency. Materials include film elements (audio and video recordings on various media, both analog and digital); research material on Bettie Page, the pornography industry in the 1950s-1960s, and mail fraud; interview transcripts and recordings; film festival programs; press; a production book; screening notes; and photographs.
    Arranged alphabetically; scripts are further arranged chronologically.
    Content Warning: Many of the images in the research materials are sexually explicit.
    - Budgets, 1995-2004 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Cast Ideas, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Character Arc, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Contracts, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Electronic Records, 1995-1997; FA_MSS_608_ER_17
      - Letters, 1992-2000 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Dailies, circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Director's Cut C -- Scene List and Notes, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Director's Statement, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - DVD Commentary, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Interviews
      - Art Amsie, undated
        - Audio Recording (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0066)
        - Transcript (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Walter Durham -- Transcript, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Frederick Freeman -- Interview Notes, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_24
      - Leon Gast, September 9, 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0103)
        - Questions, FA_MSS_608_ER_32
        - Transcript (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Buck Henry -- Interview Notes, 1995; FA_MSS_608_ER_21
      - Interviewer Notes, Updates, and Lists, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_27
      - Paula Klaw
        - Questions, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_34
        - Transcript, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Yogi Klein, 1996
        - Questions, FA_MSS_608_ER_38
        - Transcipt (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
      - Ira Kramer, 2004
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0068)
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Kingdon Lane -- Interview Notes, September 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_31
      - Harry Lear -- Transcript, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Herbert Monte Levy, October 31, 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.011)
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Milt Maculin, January 16, 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0106)
        - Questions, FA_MSS_608_ER_33
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Sam Menning, undated
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0127)
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Ed Mourhouse -- Transcript, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Billy Neal, February 4, 1996
        - Audio Recording -- Part 1 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0107)
        - Audio Recording -- Part 2 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0109)
        - Audio Recording -- Nashville -- Part 2 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0108)
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
      - Warren Nussbaum, 1995
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0122)
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Jack Page
        - Transcript, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - Questions, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_28
      - Pornaciear Society -- Transcript, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Jeff Rund, December 1995-January 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0093)
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0125)
        - Audio Recording -- #3-4 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0105)
        - Audio Recording -- Excerpts (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0123)
        - Notes and Questions, FA_MSS_608_ER_29
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Alex Siodmak -- Transcript, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_19
      - Eric Stanton, January 17, 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0104)
        - Questions, FA_MSS_608_ER_23
        - Transcript (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Greg Theakston, undated; FA_MSS_608_ER_25
      - David Walterson -- Transcript, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Charles West, August 23, 1996
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0126)
        - Transcript (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Jonnie Wilson -- Transcript, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Morris O. Wright --Transcript, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Locations and Scene Lists, 1996-2000
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_608_ER_39
      - Lists (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Music
      - Correspondence and Sheet Music, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - "Wear This Shroud" -- Arrangement and Vocal by John Cullum -- 1st and 2nd cuts -- Sermon, Vocal, and Piano, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0064)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Premiere and Publicity Schedule, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings and Reviews, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 4, Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Production Binders, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5-9, Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Production Meeting Notes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Proposals, 1993-1994; FA_MSS_608_ER_18
    - Research Materials
      - Candy Barr -- Articles, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Camera Clubs, undated
        - Articles (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - Lists of People to Interview, FA_MSS_608_ER_22
      - Censorship of Magazines -- Articles and Archival Material, 1955-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Freedom of Information Act Files on Bettie Page, Irving Klaw, and Others, 1939-1957 (Box 15, Folder 6-7, Folder 1)
      - History of Pornography -- Notes, undated; FA_MSS_608_ER_26
      - Kinsey Institute Photographs -- Photocopies, 1940-1965 (Box 17, Folder 4, Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Irving and Paula Klaw
        - Archival Material -- Correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - Notes, 1995-1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_37
        - Publications and Articles, circa 1950-1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Notes -- General Research, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Bettie Page
        - Biographical Material, 1943-1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Photographs, circa 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Publications and Articles, circa 1950-1997 (Box 17, Folder 10-13)
        - Timeline and Book Excerpts, 1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_20
      - Pin-Up History
        - Bibliography, undated; FA_MSS_608_ER_35
        - Magazines and Articles, 1950-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
      - Senate Hearings on Pornography and Juvenile Delinquency
        - Articles and Congressional Reports, 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
        - Hearing Extracts, 1955; FA_MSS_608_ER_36
      - Tempest Storm -- Articles, circa 1950-1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - John Willie
        - Archival Material -- Correspondence and Interview Transcript, 1957-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
        - Notes and Timeline, undated; FA_MSS_608_ER_30
      - Bunny Yeager -- Publications and Articles, 1952-2002 (Box 18, Folder 9, Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Screening Comments, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Screenings and Festivals, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Script by Mary Harron and Guinevere Turner
      - Early Versions and Notes, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Electronic Drafts and Outtakes, 1993-2001; FA_MSS_608_ER_40
      - First Draft, March 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6-7, Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Second Draft, January 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
      - Feedback, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Later Versions with Notes, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
      - Annotated Draft for Legal, January 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
      - Version with John's Notes, January 2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Revised, February 2003 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Shoot Photographs, 2004
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_608_ER_41
      - Prints (Box 20, Folder 11, Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Shoot Schedules, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Tape Logs, 1996
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_608_ER_42
      - Physical Copies (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Video Recordings
      - "The Ballad of Bettie Page", April 15, 2004 (Box 35, Vhs 608.0043)
      - Choreo #1, undated (Box 37, Vhs 608.0024)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Tape #53 -- Restricted Viewing -- Audio Ch. 1-2 on Circled Takes Only, May 20, 2004 (Box 33, Vhs 608.002)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Tape #58 -- Viewing Cassette -- Audio Ch. 1-2 on Circled Takes Only, September 24, 2004 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0028)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Tape #59 -- Viewing Cassette -- Audio Ch. 1-2 on Circled Takes Only -- Reshoots -- Park Scene, September 24, 2004 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0027)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Tape #64 -- Viewing Cassette -- Audio Ch. 1-2 on Circled Takes Only -- 2nd Unit, November 16, 2004 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0025)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Tape #65 -- Viewing Cassette -- Audio Ch. 1-2 on Circled Takes Only -- Reshoots -- Tibbs Studio, November 17, 2004 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0026)
      - Clowndance Productions -- Version 1 -- Mono Track Ch. 1-2, July 15, 2004 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0003)
      - Electronic Recordings, July-December 2004; FA_MSS_608_ER_58
      - Output for HBO -- Cut C -- Ch. 1 Mono Mix, October 14, 2004 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0017)
      - Selects -- Tape 1, September 23, 1996 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0145)
      - Selects -- Tape 2, September 23, 1996 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0143)
      - Selects -- Tape 3, September 23, 1996 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0144)
  - Subseries IV.D. Charlie Says, 2018; 0.44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 321.7 Megabytes in 94 computer files
    This subseries focuses on materials related to the 2018 film directed by Harron, Charlie Says. The film follows three women who were sentenced to life in prison for participating in the 1969 Charles Manson murders of Sharon Tate, her companions, and the LaBianca family. Materials include photographs, a script, correspondence, screening comments, and call lists.
    - Callsheets, 2018 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2018 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Scene List, circa 2018 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Screening Comments, 2018 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Script by Guinevere Turner, 2018 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Shoot Photographs, 2009-2018; FA_MSS_608_ER_43
  - Subseries IV.E. Shorts and Documentaries, 1994; 1.52 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 1 record carton; 2 VHS; 1 U-matic; 468 Megabytes in 3 computer files
    This subseries consists materials related to Harron's short films and documentaries. Materials include video recordings and photographs for "Streatham Ice Rink" (Harron's first short), Holding Fast (a short documentary on a Tibetan Refugee Camp in Darjeeling), and Winds of Change (a documentary by Harron and her husband, John Walsh, about South African Black artists during Apartheid).
    - Holding Fast -- Documentary by Mary Harron and John C. Walsh, April 2007; FA_MSS_608_ER_59
    - "Streatham Ice Rink"
      - Video Recording, undated (Box 37, Vhs 608.0022)
      - Video Recording, undated (Box 37, Vhs 608.0023)
    - Winds of Change, April 1994
      - Listings and Review (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Video Recording -- Cutting Copy (Box 37, U-matic 608.0054)
- Series V. Unrealized Projects, 1951-2005; 5.08 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 2 cassette boxes; 26 audiocassettes; 5 Betacam; 1.28 Megabytes in 30 computer files
  This series contains materials related to unrealized and unidentified film and writing projects. Materials include screenplay drafts, proposals, interview transcripts and recordings, correspondence, and manuscripts for "Love Affair" (about Jackson Pollock and Ruth Kligman, cowritten by Elizabeth LeCompte), "Story of O", "I'll Be Your Mirror: Stories of Women in Rock" (a book project), "True Love", "Exit Now" (cowritten by Guinevere Turner), and "Confidence" (also cowritten by Guinevere Turner). Also included are a typescript for a short story, a treatment for a music video, a consulting contract, notes for a script written by Legs McNeil and Gillian McCain, and a proposal from Dictum Publishing for a film on Gerard Sekoto.
  Arranged alphabetically by project name.
  - "Confidence", 1994
    - Correspondence, FA_MSS_608_ER_45
    - Proposal and Notes, FA_MSS_608_ER_46
    - Script by Mary Harron and Guinevere Turner
      - Electronic Versions, FA_MSS_608_ER_47
      - Undated Version (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "Exit Now"/"Millennium Blues"
    - Notes, 1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_48
    - Script by Guinevere Turner and Mary Harron -- Various Versions, 1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_49
    - Synopses, 1997-1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_50
  - "Fifth Business" -- Based on Novel by Robertson Davies
    - Outline and Memo, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_51
    - Script, Scene Breakdown, and Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "High School Confidential", undated
    - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0095)
    - Premise (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Hollywood Screenwriter Documentary -- Proposal, Notes, and Research Material, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "I'll Be Your Mirror: Stories of Women in Rock"
    - Correspondence, Proposal, and Notebook, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - General Research Material, 1964-1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Interviews and Research
      - Mae Axton -- Transcript, Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, and Research Material, 1959-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Florence Ballard -- Notes and Research Material, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Cilla Black -- Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Ruth Brown, 1980
        - Audio Recording (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0092)
        - Transcript, Notes, Synopsis/Chapter Draft, and Research Materials (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
      - Cristina -- NYC -- Audio Recording, August 25, 1982 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.01)
      - Connie De Nave -- Transcript, Notes, and Research Material, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Jenny Fabian, March 1983
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- London (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0117)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- London (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.012)
      - Marianne Faithfull
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- Paris, June 1, 1982 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0099)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- Paris, June 1, 1982 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0084)
        - Notes, Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, and Research Material, 1967-1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Connie Francis -- Transcript, Research Material, Notes, Photographs, and Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, 1961-1983 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
      - Bobbie Goforth (Bobbie Stout of WHER) -- Memphis -- Audio Recording, November 2, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0081)
      - Lesley Gore -- Transcript, Notes, and Research Material, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Wanda Jackson
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- Charlotte, November 7, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0119)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- Charlotte, November 8, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0118)
        - Transcripts, Research Material, Notes, and Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, 1971-1984 (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
      - Janis Joplin -- Transcripts of Interviews with Nik Cohn and Fran Pelzman, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Marion Keisker
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- Memphis, November 1, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0094)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- Memphis, November 1, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0069)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 3 -- Memphis, November 1, 1983 (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.006)
        - Transcript, Photographs, Synopsis/Chapter Draft, and Research Materials, 1959-1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Brenda Lee
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- Nashville, October 27, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0091)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- Nashville, October 27, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0073)
        - Synopsis/Chapter Drafts and Research Material, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 15, Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Annie Lennox -- Audio Recording, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.007)
      - Lydia Lunch -- Transcript, Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, and Research Material, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Nico -- Transcript and Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Dolly Parton -- Audio Recording, March 1, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0117)
      - Martha Reeves -- Transcript, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Helen Shapiro -- Transcript, Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, and Research Material, 1961-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Sandie Shaw -- Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Sabel Starr -- Transcript and Synopsis/Chapter Drafts, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
      - Roni Stoneman, October 18-19, 1983
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- Nashville (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0074)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- Nashville (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0096)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 3 -- Nashville (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0114)
      - Poly Styrene and Lora Logic of X-Ray Spex
        - Audio Recording, July 23, 1983 (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0062)
        - Transcript and Research Material, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Tina Turner -- Transcripts, circa 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)